Guide to the Alpha Phi Omega records, 1927-2013
Alpha Phi Omega records, 1927-2013
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Alpha Phi Omega records, 1927-2013
37-6-2876
Alpha Phi Omega (Cornell University)
8.1 cubic ft.
Logbooks, scrapbooks, member applications, minutes, correspondence, and ephemera.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Logbooks, scrapbooks, member applications, minutes, correspondence, and ephemera of a national service fraternity at Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Logbooks, scrapbooks, member applications, minutes, correspondence, slides, photographs, and ephemera of a national service fraternity at Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Alpha Phi Omega (Cornell University)
Subjects:
Student service--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Greek letter societies.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Log Books, Apr. 1973-Apr. 1987 (Box 1)
- Log Books, Apr. 1987-May 1988 (Box 2)
- Log Books (three), Spring 1994 (Box 3)
- Log Books, Spring 1995 (Box 3)
- Log Books, Fall 1996 (Box 3)
- Big-Little, Fall 1991 (Box 3)
- Big-Little, Spring 1994 (Box 3)
- Scrapbook, 1987 (Box 3)
- Past APO exploits (Box 4)
- Member applications (Box 4)
- GM and EB minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 4)
- Torch and Trefoil, 1959-1996 (Box 4)
- Foster child scrapbook (Box 4)
- 1970s items (Box 4)
  Includes Newsletter, program celebrating the Gamma Chapter's 50th Anniversary Weekend, April 16-17, 1977, photos of members.
- 2000s items (Box 4)
  Includes Gamma Gazette newsletter, member family trees, historian notes, condom labeled "got consent?".
- T-shirts, 1996 (Box 5)
- Correspondence (Box 5)
- APO seal on a notebook (Box 5)
- 3x5 membership cards (Box 5)
- Scrapbooks, 1944-1983 (Box 6)
- Scrapbooks, 1984-1990 (Box 7)
- Slides, ca. 1976-1990 (Box 8)
- Scrapbooks (Box 9)
  Annual books for Fall 2004, Fall 2007, Fall 2008, Fall 2009, Spring 2009, Spring 2010, Fall 2010, Spring 2011, Fall 2011, Spring 2012, Fall 2012, Fall 2013
- Charter (Folder In MS. Box 41)
- Alpha Phi Omega 75 Years of History 75th Anniversary disc, 2000; CD-2153 (Box 4)
- 80th Anniversary slide show, 2010; CD-2154 (Box 4)
- Photos, 2005-2007; CD-2155 (Box 4)
- Family Tree Maker discs, CD-2156-2158 (Box 4)